我从未参加过总统竞选真是太遗憾了
Too bad I could never run for president,
因为我爱做华夫饼[胡扯]
'cause1 I love waffling!
这是什么
Wha-- What is this?
奥利维亚  你一向很爱我的早餐幽默时刻
Olivia, you usually love my breakfast humor.
今天怎么闷闷不乐的  宝贝
Why so glum, sugarplum?
因为我在做代数作业
It's this algebra homework that gives me the blues.
X轴  Y轴
X-axis? Y-axis?
我干嘛要在意什么轴
Where's the 'Y'-should-I-care axis?
汉丽埃塔  你在做什么
Henrietta, what are you doing?
波杰克  也许我们该停下
BoJack, maybe we should stop.
这才刚开始  让我们在严厉的自我批判之前
We just started. Let's at least get through the first act
至少演完第一幕好吗
before we judge ourselves too harshly, huh?
我在想有没有方法让数学变得有趣
I wonder if there's a way to make math fun.
数学不可能有趣
Math will never be fun.